

# Cao Duy Quang

Apply for fulltime Teaching

#### **About Me**

Hi, my name is Quang. I'm a mentor of Mindx. Now, I want to apply for fulltime Teaching position. In the past few months, I have had experience in teaching subjects such as: Scratch, Game Maker, Web. And I have also taught subjects at the "Advance/Intensive" level.

Previously I was an automation tester and web developer. And now I decided to choose Mindx as my next workplace. I can work full time and contribute to the company.

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html

Age 23

Email <u>duyquang040720@gmail.com</u>

Phone <u>0358013596</u>

Address Tan Phu District, Ho Chi Minh City

## **Professional Skills**

HTML	
CSS	
JavaScript	
Communicate	
Scratch	
Game Marker	
Python	
Teaching	

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 2/6

### **Education**

#### Full Stack Developer from Green Academy

2020 - 2021

Trained in the Ruby programming language based on the rails framework. Exposure to HTML, CSS, Javascript, ... combined with Ruby for web design.

#### **Software Engineering** from FPT University

2018 - 2022

Trained in programming languages such as: C / C ++, Java, Python, C #, .NET, ... Regular practice at school. At the end of each theoretical course there is always a practical course. Exposure to IOT technology, learning English, Japanese, ...

Science and Mathematics from Tay Thanh High School

2015 - 2018

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html

Studied block A: natural science. Passion and research in math, logic, ...

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html

## Experience

#### **Automation Tester** at FPT Software

02/2022 - 07/2022

Participate in test automation projects. While the web development team fixed bugs, I also joined to gain experience. In addition, I also have to learn a lot by myself to be able to participate in big projects.

#### XTeacher at Mindx Technology school

05/2022 - Now

At Mindx, I am currently an mentor at Cong Hoa headquarters. I can accept to teach 3 main subjects: Scratch, Game Maker, Web and according to each level (1,2,3). The classes that I am teaching are going very well and without much difficulty. My orientation is to switch to full-time work.

127.0.0.1:5500/index.html 5/6